Sanduni Senevirathna

NO: 66/1, Kithulakanda Road Radawana.



Tel +9478-5810336

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/sanduni-senevirathna-0bb37a1a7

Email thathsarasanduni@gmail.com

01. Objective

Performance-driven and results-oriented software engineer with two year working experience, seeking to use OOP, Machine Learning and Data Science to deliver coding excellence in designing, testing, and development software with software troubleshooting experiences. And also an effective team player with excellent analytical skill and important ability to solve complex problem.

02. Educational Qualifications

- Bachelor's Degree, Wayamba University Sri Lanka Jan 2015 Jan 2019
 - -Computer Science (Special) with first class.
 - GPA 3.7
 - Relevant Coursework:
 - 1. Software based project on Online Assessment System using PHP, HTML, JS, MySQL(in 2018)
 - 2.E-commerce based project Online Job Portal System Using PHP, HTML ,MySQL(in 2018)
 - Learnt Mathematical and Statistics(in 2015-2017)

03. Professional Qualification

- Advance English Course at English Language Teaching Unit -2018, Wayamba University of Sri Lanka.
- Business English Course at English Language Teaching Unit -2018, Wayamba University of Sri Lanka.
- English Language Proficiency Course at English Language Teaching Unit -2018, Wayamba University of Sri Lanka.
- Completed Certificate Course on Google Cloud Product Fundamentals-2019, COURSERA
- Completed Certificate Course on Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure-2019, COURSERA
- Completed Certificate Course on AI For Everyone-2020, COURSERA
- Completed Certificate Course on Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python)-2018, COURSERA

04. Work Experience

- Software Engineer, E-SOFTO, Colombo 07 Jun 2019 Present
 - -Develop object oriented software design for construction industry's leading project
 - -Develop and customize software product for diverse client base
- Software Intern, Software Engineering Corporation, Nawala Jan 2019 Jun 2019
 - -Contributed to development of 4 projects using Java, JavaScript, Python
 - -Participated in code review
 - -Provided development support

05. Extra-Curricular Activities

I. Leadership

- Committee Member 2019, IEEE Women in Engineering Student Branch Affinity Group of Wayamba University of Sri Lanka.
- Committee Member 2016-2019, ZEST Society (Knowledge Sharing Program) of Wayamba University of Sri Lanka.
- Publication Team Member-2017-2019, SEDS Society of Wayamba University of Sri Lanka.

II. Volunteering

• Brand Ambassador – IEEE ,2017-Present

III. Others

- Participated ENGIMA TRIAS -2019, Association of Computing & Information System Students, Faculty of Applied Sciences, Wayamba University of Sri Lanka.
- Attend Software Engineering Professional Hackathon, 2020
- Runner's up in Team Contest and Video Contest-2019 IEEE Sri Lanka Section Student | Young Professional | WIE Congress
- Selected as Finalist in ACTINSPACE-2019,Internationalo Innovation Contest Colombo-Sri Lanka ,Space Agency of France(CNES),Work as Team Leader
- Participated in the virtual mini-hackathon HomeAlone-2019 organized by the Students' Union of the Faculty of Information Technology, University of Moratuwa.
- Participated in coding competition Cup-a-Code ,2019, organized by IEEE CS Student Branch Chapter NSSCE,IEEE CS Student Branch Chapter MESCE,IEEE Student Branch of Rajarata University of Sri Lanka ,IEEE CS Student Branch Chapter Panimalar Institute of Technology

06. Special Skills

• Proficiency in Language:

English - Fluent

Tamil - Fair

• Technical Skills

Agile Project Management

Customer Web And Mobile Application

Database Programming

Data Science

• Presentation Skill

07. Personal Details

Full name : Hewa Gamage Sanduni Thathsara Senevirathna

Address: NO: 66/1, Kithulakanda Road, Radawana.

DOB : 18.12.1997 NIC : 978533205V

Gender : Female

Mobile NO: +94785810336

08. Non-related referees

I. E.M.H.J.Edirisinghe,

Senior Lecture,

Date

Department of English Language Teaching, Wayamba University of Sri Lanka, Kuliyapitiya.

Mobile: +94 71 9891224 Office: +94 37 2283155

Email:hemanthawusl@gmail.com

II. S.K.Perera

Senior Software Engineer

Software Engineering Cooperation

Nawala.

Mobile: +94715286789

Email:perera1234@gmail.com

Signature

I am hereby certify that the above particulars furnished by e are true and correct to the best of my knowledge.	
•••••	***************************************